Vedran Arnautovic

Senior UX Designer

527 Brunswick Street Fitzroy North VIC 3068

phone 0434 490 076 web vedran.io email hello@vedran.io twitter @vedranio

I'm a user centred designer with over 10 years' experience, focusing on UX design, usability, interaction design and user research.

I'm interested in development of design teams through mentoring and integration of modern design tools and practices into their workflows.

Experience

SEEK

Jan 2014 - present

Senior UX Designer

I've led design on key initiatives within SEEK's advertiser portfolio, often crossing over both sides of the marketplace.

My work is a mixture of tactical projects where I closely work with small agile teams, and more strategic efforts where I've worked with senior leaders to define the future of SEEK's products.

// Keywords

UX, UI, workshop facilitation, user research, usability testing, prototyping, agile, lean UX

Freelance

Sep 2016 – present

Freelance UX designer

Gymsales

I lead design for Gymsales, working closely with the CEO and the dev team.

// Keywords

UI, information architecture, iPad, animation design

Rubicon

I ran a design sprint for Rubicon's Dutch clients and developed a prototype for the solution we came up with during the sprint.

// Keywords google design sprint, workshop facilitation, wireframe, prototype, coaching, mentoring

Kolektiv

Over a period of 6 months, I coached Kolektiv's product team on usability testing and lean UX practices.

// Keywords usability testing, lean UX, coaching, mentoring

SMS

Sep 2010 – Jan 2014

Consultant (UX designer and BA)

During my time at SMS, I worked for three clients

- UX Designer and BA (NAB)
- UX Designer (NAB)
- Interface Designer and BA (BP)

Internally, I was appointed the Customer Experience (CX) lead for Victoria kickstarted the development of our CX capability.

// Keywords
Usability testing, UI design, workshop facilitation, journey mapping, interface design

Leica

Feb 2009 – Sep 2010 Melbourne

System Design Engineer & BA

Upon returning to Melbourne, I worked with Leica's software team and got an opportunity to define a number of design improvements based on my research in the field.

// Keywords
UI design, wireframes, system design, business analysis

Leica

Feb 2007 – Feb 2009 London

System Design Engineer

A career shaping opportunity allowed me to spend two years researching how our clients and support teams interacted with our instruments, and to use those findings to design better solutions for them.

// Keywords
user research, contextual enquiry, process design,
system design

Vision BioSystems

Jan 2004 - Feb 2007

Software Engineer

I started out very technical, developing software for medical devices. Working in an organisation with no designers created a window of opportunity to start designing and show initiative to test software with users.

// Keywords software developer, UI design, user testing

Education

Univ. of Melbourne

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

1999 - 2004

Univ. of Melbourne

Bachelor's degree, Mechatronics

1999 - 2004

Tools

Sketch, Adobe CC, Marvel, Invision, Axure, Principle, Morae, Framer.js, CSS, HTML, Javascript, Github + anything else I need to learn.